<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>excellence on UCR PostdocAssoc</title>
    <link>https://rpa.ucr.edu/tags/excellence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in excellence on UCR PostdocAssoc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>postdoc@ucr.edu (UCR PostdocAssoc)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>postdoc@ucr.edu (UCR PostdocAssoc)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rpa.ucr.edu/tags/excellence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UCR Postdoc Awards for Excellence</title>
      <link>https://rpa.ucr.edu/post/2023-11-29-awards-for-excellence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>postdoc@ucr.edu (UCR PostdocAssoc)</author>
      <guid>https://rpa.ucr.edu/post/2023-11-29-awards-for-excellence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Graduate Division, the Office of Research and the Riverside Postdoc Association is pleased to announce the call for the annual Postdoc Awards for Excellence. This award honors postdocs who have demonstrated excellence in research, mentorship and service to the community. &lt;strong&gt;The awards will consist of a plaque and a $1000 check to be awarded at the Graduate Division’s Award Ceremony&lt;/strong&gt;. We are seeking nomination letters from department chairs, faculty, students, and postdocs in support of an excellent individual in your area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eligibility Criteria&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a current postdoc at UCR and have held the position for at least 6 months in any of UCR’s departments and must be holding the position at the time of application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work described must have taken place while at UCR.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional service to the community does not have to be associated with UCR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Apply&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submit a research statement describing your research achievements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submit a personal statement to include activities such as mentorship, philosophy on diversity and outreach activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statements are a maximum 2 pages, 1 inch margin, 12pt Arial, single space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submit a CV (NIH biosketch or NSF formatting allowed).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Letters of support from UCR mentor and/or mentees, such as current or former students should address how the mentoring relationship provided training or boosted their professional development, and describe the positive impact on their own scholarship and well-being. We encourage the authors to use specific examples in their letter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The deadline for the 2024-2025 academic year is January 16th, 2024. Please submit your application to the Postdoc Awards &lt;a href=&#34;https://form.jotform.com/230466432058959&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
